

## CONTACT

- +628-5714-3093-86
- ✓ agung.priyadi96@gmail.com
- Yes Kp.Bencongan, Kab. Tangerang
- https://github.com/agungpriya di1997/Portfolio

### **EDUCATION**

2015 - 2019 UNIVERSITAS RAHARJA

- Bachelor of Teknik Informatika
- GPA: 2.86 / 4.0

2012 - 2015 SMK YUPPENTEK 7 TANGERANG

• School of Teknik Komputer Jaringan

#### **SKILLS**

- Teamwork
- Problem Solving
- Time Management
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

## HARD SKILLS

- HTML, JavaScript, CSS
- Jira, Jnkins, Ms. Office, Katalon, Postman
- CI,Boostrap,Wordpress
- Github, Firebase
- Sql,Mysql

# **AGUNG PRIYADI**

## IT SQA | WEB DEVELOPER | ADMINISTRATION

#### **PROFILE**

Hello, my name is Agung Priyadi. I graduated from Universitas Raharja in 2019 with a degree in Computer Science. Currently, I reside in Tangerang. My most recent work experience was as an IT Quality Assurance at Bank Mandiri. I have skills in computer-related fields such as Web Programming, IT SQA, and Administration.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **BPJS Kesehatan**

Software Tester

- Creating a User Manual
- · Creating a Test Scenario
- · Perform application testing
- Creating a Testing Document
- Reporting Bugs

#### Bank Mandiri (Persero) Tbk

Jan 2023 - Dec 2023

Sep 2024 - Now

IT Quality Assurance

- Testing banking application and web application.
- Create testing scenario (positive, negative).
- ecute all testing scenario and create documentation for the results.
- Distribute bugs to programmers.
- · Monitor bugs handling and perform rechecking.
- · Make documentation for each activity of testing.
- Implementation all scenario testing with users at User Acceptance Test (UAT).

#### PT Pancamitra Packindo

Jan 2022 - Jul 2022

Admin design

- Make a sample carton product design for suppliers.
- Communicating with suppliers about the desired carton design.
- printing carton sample

#### PT Sumber Alfaria Trijaya Tbk

Feb 2020 - May 2021

Admin Warehouse

- Input store orders to the warehouse
- Input store item returns to suppliers
- · Create daily and monthly stock reports
- · Checking goods
- Make a road letter
- · Tidy up the archives

## **LANGUAGES**

• English (Fluent)